embibe.com 2015-05-28

# Embibe.com - Privacy policy

### INTRODUCTION

We, at 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

"Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Indiavidual Learning Private Limited's Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

### COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.

### THIRD PARTY SERVICES

Third parties provide certain services available on www.embibe.com on Indiavidual Learning Private Limited's behalf. 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' may provide information, including Personal Information, that 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' collects on the Web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' maintains its Web site and mailing lists. 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on Indiavidual Learning Private Limited's behalf.

'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Indiavidual Learning Private Limited's behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Indiavidual Learning Private Limited's policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.

### YOUR CONSENT

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Indiavidual Learning Private Limited's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' collects Personal Information on the Web.

### INFORMATION SECURITY

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.

We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

### UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of our services.

### INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people (save with your consent) or non- affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' communicate with you about offers from 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Indiavidual Learning Private Limited's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.

### CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the laws prevalent in India to protect personal information about you.

### CHANGE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

To update, correct or review your Personal Information that was previously provided by you to use, you have the following options:

If you have signed up with us and have an account, you may make the changes on your account profile page by signing in and saving the said changes/ modfications. Any change/ modification made by you, will be reflected on the website.

In the alternative, you may write to us at the following address:

Indiavidual Learning Pvt Ltd.  
Unit 5, Jetha Compound, Byculla East Mumbai - 400027  
Maharashtra, India  

Please mention the changes to be made clearly and we will try and update the requite changes/ modifications as requested by you in your letter.

### SENSITIVE INFORMATION

Kindly do not send us or disclose any sensitive personal information for example information relating to your racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health etc. on or through the site or otherwise to us.

### AUTHORIZED STATEMENT

This Privacy Policy represents the sole privacy statement of our practices with respect to the collection of Personal Information through the Sites and our use and disclosure of this information. Any other statement or summary with respect to any privacy policy published by any third party shall have no binding or legal effect whatsoever.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' reserves the right to update, change or modify this policy at any time. The policy shall come to effect from the date of such update, change or modification.

Indiavidual Learning Private Limited shall not be liable for any loss or damage sustained by reason of any disclosure (inadvertent or otherwise) of any information concerning the user's account and / or information relating to or regarding online transactions using credit cards / debit cards and / or their verification process and particulars nor for any error, omission or inaccuracy with respect to any information so disclosed and used whether or not in pursuance of a legal process or otherwise.

'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement at the contact address given at the website. Should there be any concerns about contravention of this Privacy Policy, 'Indiavidual Learning Private Limited' will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same.

Note: The terms in this agreement may be changed by Indiavidual Learning Private Limited at any time. Indiavidual Learning Private Limited is free to offer its services to any client/prospective client without restriction
